AMY LAM

amyhlam2@gmail.com | amyhlam.github.io

SUMMARY

Self-motivated and enthusiastic worker with experience in web development, management, healthcare, and customer service. Strong willingness to learn and very attentive to accuracy and details. Good at multi-tasking with excellent organizational skills. Have experience working with many different teams at all organizational levels and diverse backgrounds in an efficient and effective manner.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES

SYSTEMS & TOOLS

Visual Studio, MongoDB, MySQL, Git, Firebase, Strapi

FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES

JavaScript, HTML, Python, SQL

React, Node.js, Express, jQuery, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, SASS/SCSS

EXPERIENCE

THAO & HAIR

Huntington Beach, CA

Web Developer September 2023 - Present (Contract)

- Design and develop a responsive and user-friendly website showcasing the client's work and offered services.
- Continue to maintain and update the website as requested per client.

PACIFIC COAST HOSPITALITY & MANAGEMENT LLC

Westminster, CA *May 2022 – June 2023*

Assistant Project Manager

- Created the timeline and delegated tasks that needed to be completed.
- Assisted in cost-benefit analysis to stay within budget while generating the most profitable outcome.
- Ensured that all operations of setting up the rental property proceeded in a timely manner and within budget.

BANNER DEL E. WEBB MEDICAL CENTER

Sun City West, AZ

Certified Nursing Assistant

March 2021 – December 2021

January 2018 – July 2020

July 2015 – August 2016

- Provided high-quality patient care by assisting with activities of daily living, hygiene, feeding, dressing, as well as checked vitals and blood glucose levels.
- Worked closely with the nursing staff, PAs, NPs, and physicians on the medical-surgical unit to appropriately implement care for the patients, as well as floating to other departments when needed.
- Maintained a comfortable and clean environment for every patient while adhering to all hospital safety guidelines, protocols, and regulations.
- Accurately charted all patient interactions in electronic health records system.

HEALTHSCRIBE

Phoenix, AZ

Medical Scribe
Documented all necessary and relevant information during a patient's visit in the clinic for multiple physicians.

Document an necessary and relevant mormation during a patients visit in the crime for multiple physicians.

• Maintained proper records of medical histories and any procedures done in the office using AllScripts and Athena.

REFINED NAILS & SPA Front Desk Coordinator

Glendale, AZ

• Served as an enthusiastic and welcoming first point of contact for clients, as well as dealt with any issues.

- Scheduled appointments in person and by phone according to client and nail technician availability.
- Carried out transactions using the cash register, including cash and card payments.
- Created fliers and online ads to attract new clients, as well as inform them about any ongoing promotions through social media.
- Responded to Yelp and Facebook reviews to ensure excellent customer service.

AMERICA READS

Scottsdale, AZ
February 2016 – May 2016

• Tutored children after school in math, reading, and science by creating hands on activities and quizzes to test their knowledge.

PROJECTS

THAO & HAIR

THAOANDHAIR, NETLIFY, APP

Multi-page, responsive website created for client built on React framework. The site includes a beautiful landing page, as well as all the necessary information and links that the business requires.

LET'S GET COOKIN'

GITHUB.COM/AMYHLAM/LETS-GET-COOKIN

A full-stack web application created to share recipes built using Javascript, EJS, and Bootstrap. The project uses MongoDB and has user authentication capabilities.

WEB PORTFOLIO - https://amyhlam.github.io

EDUCATION

ARIZONA STATE UNIVERSITY Bachelor of Science, Biochemistry

Tempe, AZ